<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kiwi</title>
    <link>http://www.thekiwi.online/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kiwi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.thekiwi.online/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.thekiwi.online/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.thekiwi.online/about/</guid>
      <description>What is KIWI? The KIWI is a utility token, rather than a security. The KIWI will be used as the preferred payment method in exchange of all products, services and tools being developed by Liberation Online as well as a growing number of other businesses.
The KIWI is an open source mineable ERC20 / ERC918 token. The KIWI is a currency that anyone can mine, buy and sell. The KIWI is also going to be the only accepted currency for a new ICO model being developed by Liberation Online that will bring a new standard in fairness and transparency when it comes to raising funds on the blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started</title>
      <link>http://www.thekiwi.online/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.thekiwi.online/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Currently, difficulty is low enough that CPU mining is viable! So you can let your GPUs work away mining ETH or other coins, while putting the CPU to work as well.
Mining Software To mine KIWI you need to download and run special software that has been built for the task of mining. Currently there are 2 miners that can mine KIWI.
 MVis Token Miner - https://github.com/mining-visualizer/MVis-tokenminer/releases COSMiC - https://bitbucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>http://www.thekiwi.online/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.thekiwi.online/faqs/</guid>
      <description>Why can&#39;t I see KIWI in my address on Etherscan?    When you sucessfully mine KIWI, the contract adds you to it&#39;s list of KIWI owners. This is held within the contract. However, there is no easy way for Etherscan to know that your account has KIWI until you either receive KIWI from another address or you send KIWI to another address.   How can I see how many KIWI I have?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>